jimsmarketingblog.com 2018-08-26

# Privacy Policy | Jim's Marketing Blog

### Who we are

This is the blog of marketing mentor, [Jim Connolly](https://jimsmarketingblog.com/about-2/).

### The personal data I collect and why

**Contact forms:** The only personal information collected here, is the information you send me via our contact forms.

If for any reason you have used a contact form on this site and would like me to delete your form data, just [request it here](mailto:jimconnollymarketing@gmail.com) and it will be deleted immediately.

Jim’s Marketing Blog is protected by internationally respected security experts, [Sucuri](https://sucuri.net/). They have a strong firewall, between the server where the blog (and all it’s data) is, and anyone accessing the site. **No personally identifiable form data or metadata is retained locally on our devices; it’s exclusively online, behind Sucuri’s world-class security.**

### Cookies

Because this site doesn’t have a comments section or serve advertising, we have very limited use of cookies. [This is our cookie policy, in full.](https://jimsmarketingblog.com/about-2/cookie-policy-and-disclosure/)

### Analytics

This site uses Google Analytics to measure activity on the site. No personally identifiable information is collected.

### Who we share your data with

No one.

### How long we retain your data

If you use a contact form, the form content and metadata is retained for 1 year. You can ask for your data to be deleted at any time and requests will be dealt with immediately.

### What rights you have over your data

Unless you have sent me a message via a contact form, this site collects no personally identifiable information on you. If for any reason you have used a contact form on this site and would like me to delete it (no reason required), just [request it here](mailto:jimconnollymarketing@gmail.com) and it will be deleted immediately.

### What data breach procedures we have in place

Jim’s Marketing Blog is protected from data breaches by internationally respected security experts, [Sucuri](https://sucuri.net/). They have a strong firewall, between the server where the blog (and all it’s data) is, and anyone accessing this site. **No personally identifiable information is retained locally on our devices; it’s exclusively online, behind Sucuri’s security**.
